how to convert any low resolution photo
into high resolution in photoshop
here is the very low resolution photo we
can't use this to share online due to
the lack of quality
but luckily you can improve image
resolution in photoshop with a simple
technique
open preferences from the edit menu then
choose technology previews
in here enable preserve details 2.0
update
hit ok
then go to the image size option and
increase the resolution of the image
check to resample and choose to preserve
details 2.0
if the final image looks too much sharp
try reduce noise slider to balance
between smoothness and texture
here is high resolution image
thanks for watching
please subscribe